Hello student friends, welcome to
your Goodwills, chapters have been spent on you in IC 38 or Chapter
and the
question answers in it are the second part of which you are seeing. The
first question is which of the following is
ineligible to enter into a life insurance contract?
Business owner, ignorant person, housewife,
government employee, answer number, number,
two unknown
persons, second question is which of the following
acts
shows adherence to the principle of Supreme Change Panacha,
false information regarding the known medical condition in the insurance proposal.
Not to disclose the material truth condition known in the dimensional proposal form. To disclose the
physical true condition known in the dimensional proposal form. To
fill in the dimensional week statement or answer
synonym
number three To
disclose the physical true condition known in the dimensional proposal form.  The
third question is insurable health or in
relation to
which of the following is not eligible? Husband,
wife, single, taking insurance, friend, single,
owner, employee, taking insurance policy, the
answer is synonym number three, friend,
single, not eligible for insurance, then the fourth is insurable health in life insurance.
The
correct answer is: Synonym Number:
After taking one dimension, the fifth question is: In the following
context, find out the reason for near death,
Ajay Ghodyavar Pado and his readers'
bones.  While turning he would have fallen into the water and
he would have been diagnosed with pneumonia and would have been
admitted to the hospital and if
pneumonia had brought him close to death, he would have thought about the cause. Pneumonia is the answer to the problem of horse and liver.
Surgery is the answer to the
synonym number of both the readers of the disease of the human body. Is it
necessary to have insurable health in life? Is it necessary to take insurance?
In case of life insurance, insurable health is
not necessary. On the one hand,
buying an insurance policy or paying insurance is the answer. The answer is
synonym number one.  The seventh
question is the risk in the economic market. Diversified
activities, how is the risk reduced? The idea of
pooling funds from various sources and investing in one place,
keeping the gap in mind, investing in safe assets,
risk reduction.  The
eighth question is which of the following life
insurance business component does not have a life insurance business
component? Neither is the asset risk
mutual element considered. Seventy seven is the synonym number
four
meaning is the ninth question is HLV. The concept was
created by Kelly Dr. Marton Leiter King
Baron Buffett Professor B. Benner George Soros level
answer is synonym number
three medicine question is Which of the following insurance
plan has saving component? There is no reduction or strange thing in
term insurance plan gift plan whole
life plan.
Question 1: Which of the following things
cannot be considered as property? Car,
human life, air, house, boat, yoga.
Answer is:  The
following events are
classified under injury, not being able to die, very
young death, very early death, natural need, need, disability, unconsciousness, the
answer is
synonym number three,
13th question. Which of the following statements is
true? First, life insurance policy means
indemnity agreement, whereas
life insurance policy means assurance agreement in ordinary dimension. Life insurance policy means assurance agreement.
Ordinary dimension
means indemnity agreement. The
event which is protected in ordinary dimension is certain and
dense. In ordinary insurance, the
probability of an event increasing with the duration is true.
Answer is Synonym
Number. Both life insurance policies are agreements of provision
whereas ordinary insurance policies are agreements of indemnity.
14th question is which of the following
method defines the amount required by a person?  The
traditional
method that helps in estimating human economic value is life term
proposal human life value future life
value answer option number three human
life
value young man is estimated as compared to adult man, which of the following options gives the current
situation and
which of the following options gives young people
are very dependent on paying more amount of money adult man can
pay more amount of money mortality rate or
related to it Mortality rate and age have a very close
relationship Answer option number
three is related to mortality rate as many as one and a
quarter question which of the following stop
value insurance is not a benefit, safe
and worry-free, face-saving discipline
arises  The
17th question is
which of the following is the stopping price, the profit is
not the profit, inflation is the result of the loss, the loss is the loss in
the beginning of the year, the fund accumulation is decreasing, the
shortage is causing worry.  Answer: Free investment or Answer:
Which of the following packs gives tax?
Question 2: Saving is both the two types of
decisional
reduction, donating and saving, spending
and saving, consumption, carrying forward and
reducing liquidity. Synonym number four is consumption,
carrying forward and reducing liquidity.
Patel is the most important post-retirement
student, when the ascendant is rising, at the same time, the
answer is synonym number
one, after retirement, Eastern Ch, the
most importance point of savings is Patel. The 23rd question is the
relationship between the period available for investment and the investment, there is no
relation between the investment period, the more investment period is more, the more investment is, the more investment is, the more investment is, the more
investment is, the
investment is the bigger one, the more tax is, the
more tax is, the answer is synonym number
four, the 24th question is which of the following packaged
business products or categories?
Bank security deposit can be classified under which of the following contingent products?
Bank security deposit can be
classified under which of the following contingent products?  The
answer is the synonym serial number three even
part which of the following assets can be
classified under financial products
bank security the
synonym number four even part or the eligible answer is the dash meaning the
27th question Dash means to
create a meaning for a period of time goods and
services price normal falling growth in situ
inflation stability hyperinflation The eligible
answer is inflation 28th question is
which of the following voluntary deeds to generate
more and more creation not
reconstruction debt transfer investment re
Creation Dimension Purchase or This Answer is Synonym
Number Four Dimension Purchase
29th Question Which of the following is the intangible
product Car House Life Dimension Saban Tar
Answer is Synonym Number Three Life Dimension
Third Question is Sampoorna Jeevan Vimsathi Ada
Kelela Vima Haapta Mudat Vima Sa  The 32nd question is for your life insurance, you have filled the insurance
week for your
life insurance, you have filled in the dash of the insurance week for the increased
amount of the insurance week, the death has decreased, the policy margin has increased, the profit margin has been increased, the
black money has been compensated, the life insurance policy has increased, the life insurance policy has increased, the death has increased, the policy margin has
decreased, the amount has been paid, more than the insurance week has been paid.  The
33rd question is which of the following
synonyms is related to term insurance scheme?   The life
insurance plan has the renewal capacity.
All term insurance plans have the capacity for renewal. Inherent
disability, old age [ __ ] term insurance is the
only policy that one keeps purchasing.
Similarly, one keeps purchasing other policies as well.
Term insurance plan has a
provision to change the whole life insurance plan. The
correct answer is the synonym number
three i.e. term insurance is the only policy that one keeps
purchasing. Same policy is the only policy that one keeps
buying for the old age. This is the only meaning.
Independent 34th question is that the
term insurance policy is decreasing, the insurance to be paid over time
increases and continues to decrease as the weeks go on.  Layers go bananas
Answer option number three
remains the same  The
36th question is: The
primary purpose of life insurance production is tax
relief; a safe way to invest;
personal productive capacity; to
protect against loss of economic value; to
accumulate wealth; the answer is to:
And there is a
budget of one person in the district, there is a huge demand
but their budget is small, one
person is a big product, they
give a big offer and they ask someone to buy the limited quantity.
Or should I
ask someone to do it? Answer: There is a
need for such a person in the district, but
his style letter is
small. 38 Questions:
Which of the following statements is wrong in relation to the term insurance policy? The term
insurance policy is decreasing. The insurance protection period, the
benefit, the insurance amount keeps decreasing, the insurance week
amount keeps decreasing as per the age, the insurance week is the same, the
entire duration is the same, the
life insurance plan is decreasing, the entire duration is the same, the life
insurance scheme is decreasing, the other
answer is the synonym number three, the insurance weeks are the same, the
entire duration is the same, the
29th question is term insurance assurance.
Which of the following laws is
ineligible in this respect: It has only the
benefit of death as its component, it has only the
benefit of survival as its component, it has the benefit of death
and survival as its component?  If
both the components are living benefit, then the question is like the insurance plan. The
answer is the level or the answer is the synonym
number three. It has both the components of death benefit and
survival benefit. The
40th question is which of the following is an example of an
annuity insurance plan? An example of an endowment insurance plan is a salvation plan, a
loan, a life insurance plan, a
money-lost plan, a whole life insurance
plan, the answer is a money-lost plan, 21
Question is the reference to the resource allocation within an additional allocation, which can be carried
forward for some period, the
meaning of the modification of the allocation, the allocation
modification.  Watt Pache Diversification level Answer
Synonym Number Both Over a period of time Resource
allocation Question 42 Which of the following is
limited to the traditional life dimension production
One or the policy is high Both are
clear and visible methods of calculating the overall value
Three  Guaranteed Reserve and Savings Value
Factor Fourth Layer Rate is not easy to fix The
answer is Option Number Four
Layer Rate is not easy to fix 43rd Question
Which of the following methods is a traditional method to help determine the amount of insurance a person needs
Human Economic Value
Life Term Offer Human Life Value
Future Life Value Level Qualified Answer is
Option Number Three Human Life Value
44th Question Which of the following is
most likely to buy a variable life insurance policy People who are born in the
fixed market are
people who die and who do
not get injured in equal part
Information about the overall market  People who are well-informed and comfortable,
common people, young people, level answer synonym,
three even parts, people who are comfortable with market knowledge,
question
is Universal Life Policy
USA, Great Britain, Germany, France,
etc. Synonym number one
USA 4 Close release of life insurance production
Context is the financial year Life insurance is
related to the same part of life production
Aggregation of protection and savings components
Protection and savings or division of components Other
Synonym number four Protection and savings or division of
components The
47th question is
Which of the following clauses are true in relation to ULIP? The units are determined
according to the basic fundamental equation.
ULIPs are transparent
products. Answer: Synonym number three.
48 Question Is it or is it different? All of the following have the
characteristics of variable life dimension.
Variable life dimension is a specific idea, not
flexible but fixed. There is no limit value, we have
no savings.  The reserve amount is limited to where the
policy holder dies and what is the minimum benefit that the policy holder gets if he dies.
I thought about whether all other
features of the life are different and the eligible answer is
what is the option number? The
49th question is that there is flexibility and not certainty. In the
context of universal life insurance, the following policy
is eligible. Both the provisions allow the policy holder to
fill in the black money and change the policy.  What is the
wrong
answer? What is the synonym?
Preservation of value Loan Budla eviction
Default answer is Home loan Ghena sa
Financial protection Purvani Like this or
in the video you have spent 50 questions In the previous
video you would have spent 50 questions Thank
you m